Hey it's me Celine, welcome to a new video here. It's going to be a catsuit video and
it's going to be colorful because I have three catsuits. They're all the same model but I bought
them in three different colors. Why? Because I thought let's mix things up. I saw them at the
sale on the Foggy Web shop and yeah you can decide which color suits me best. So stay tuned,
I will change into the first one so we can get started.
The first catsuit I decided on the green one. I think yeah it's kind of a dark forest green with
a hint of turquoise maybe and I quite like the design because it's almost like a corset part
look-alike at least here in the top part and we have these visible seams here along the body
but today i want to style all the catsuits so i think i'll add some accessories in a different
color i still need to get rid of the tag let's hope i'm not cutting my hair or whatever
So for the accessories I will go with the red, nice contrast color.
Okay I need to get rid of my socks first so I can get into the shoes, they are open.
I'm mostly too lazy to open the straps and they are too wide anyway, I would need additional
holes here so i can just slip into them this way
and now for the harness it was a birthday gift from her wishlist
so thank you for that i still need to figure out whether to open or close it
Okay, this is the full look and I quite like the contrast of the green and the red.
I noticed since I'm recording in a different location today that I don't have a mirror
here on which I can see myself.
So this is the mirror.
I do like it. Nice. I'm usually not the biggest fan of green. I don't know, I always think it
doesn't work with my hair but surprise it does. So I quite like the jumpsuit here. Close it.
oh it's warm it's not a thin material it's four letter and it's really soft on the inside so
starting to sweat but let's do the rating rate it in the comments from one to five
and i will change into the next one and we'll see how many votes the green one gets
For the second one I chose the black jumpsuit and I can tell that the fabric is a bit more stretchy than the green one.
And we have these seams here again which I really like. I think they give a bit of structure to the catsuit.
And it looks like it's turned inside out but it isn't. It's meant to be this way.
Putting my socks on again so I don't get any hate comments about putting on shoes without socks.
These are my favorite favorite, the Monia boots. So comfy I can only like say it again and again.
Festivals and concerts, these are the ones.
okay now I'm taller and I also have a belt I also love putting this belt on top of everything
now one thing I noticed now is that the zipper is not really stainless steel so compared to the
belt it's more gray and a bit more dull not shiny I think it would have looked way better if the
zipper would have been like a shiny metal as well but that's not the way it is this is the look
with the heels and I do have a long leather coat I want to try and see if it works together
not something I usually do normally I have my short leather jackets but
I always forget about this one
With wearing this coat I instantly feel like a special agent.
The other day I took pictures with this coat in Laundry Aluminium.
But I think this is a completely different look.
So instead of running to the mirror again I am using the display on my camera here to
take a look at least at the top part.
Because I can't see it properly in full of course but I think it's okay.
I think it works.
Okay cross checking in the mirror and yeah I think I like it.
It's better with the zipper open.
I thought so because otherwise it's too much.
Fun! Fun look! I did not expect it to work this well together. It's also cool it's like
I opened the coat a bit more. Almost like a robe or dress. I'm making nice hips here,
especially with the belt underneath. Okay don't forget to rate this one in the comments one to
five and I will change into the red one now last one the last one and I took
pictures with this one the other day on the beam behind the camera I can show you
the picture I think it was really cool especially with the color here in this
room the colorful lights but now I have to put on some shoes
Now for accessories I can play it safe of course and use the belt I wore on the
starting outfit as part of the starting outfit. Because it's really versatile and simply cool.
Like this.
oh by the way I lied in the beginning there's a difference I have a different
sit on here it's black and red more fancy fancier than the other two
I still prefer them open and the brand foggy is from Romania and I ordered as I said I ordered
them in sale as you can see they don't have a cross zipper so they're basically fashion jumpsuits
and they haven't been in the workout section or anything else on the home page but in just like
the general clothing section and I'm going out on a limp here but I'm saying that in Germany
you wouldn't simply wear something like this in everyday life except for if you maybe live in
Berlin or Munich or Dusseldorf whatever but if you're watching this video and you're from Romania
please tell me do Romanian women wear these kind of jumpsuits in their everyday life do you see
them out on the street. I am curious. Now with this outfit and the flat boots and my belt pouches
here I feel like I can go out exploring and play Fallout or whatever. But yeah, that was it. The
last catsuit. Don't forget again to rate this in the comments. One to five. I'm not going to tell
you what my favorite is. You have to decide it on your own. By the way if you
want to see more of these catsuits full picture sets, a lot of different other
picture sets, lottery catsuits, latex, head over to my Patreon because I am
posting a lot there, a lot of behind the scenes and outfits I'm not showing on
YouTube and since my channel got demonetized a few years ago I have a
small community over there so if you want to support me and get a lot of
photos to watch then head over there and I will see you in the next video here on
my channel or I will see you over on patreon you can also message me there
and yeah have a nice day see you around bye